# SARAH CONWAY

Senior software engineer, frontend web developer, senior website manager, technical support engineer, developer advocate, conference organizer, diversity committee chair, program organizer, social media manager, and copy editor are just some of the technical hats I've worn in 10+ years of professional experience. For a personal look into who I am and my involvement in the open source community, check out my interview featured in #PostgresFriends "PostgreSQL Person of the Week".

## **EXPERIENCE**

Crunchy Data, Remote - Senior Software Engineer

MARCH 2017 - PRESENT

- Senior Frontend Developer Full project ownership and collaboration on distributed/remote teams for multiple frontend applications and websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Reactstrap, React JS, TypeScript, Hugo, and a variety of other frontend technologies that can be found under my Technical Skills.
- Senior Software Engineer Developed the <u>Crunchy Data PostgreSQL Operator</u> and <u>Crunchy Data Container Suite</u>, containerization technology that provides a high-level abstraction and solution for rapid creation and simplified management of PostgreSQL clusters, using Kubernetes, OpenShift, Docker, Go, JSON, & SQL. Wrote public-facing documentation for both projects.
- Technical Support Engineer Participated in a 24x7 support rotation providing real-time customer support to users from all technical backgrounds, from sales experts to database administrators, using OSTicket. Support was provided for high availability PostgreSQL in on-premise, public & private cloud, and container environments. Wrote technical support guides for internal teams & customers.
- Presented: Containerizing PostgreSQL for Cloud Natives Video
- Presented: Don't Panic: Use the PostgreSQL Operator for Kubernetes and OpenShift - <u>Video</u> - <u>Slides</u>
- Presented: A Kubernetes Operator for PostgreSQL <u>Video</u> <u>Slides</u>
- Published: Blogpost <u>pqBackRest Performing Backups on a</u>
   Standby Cluster

#### PostgreSQL, Remote - Evangelist

JANUARY 2012 - PRESENT

- PostgreSQL US Diversity Committee Chair [Oct 2019 Present] -Program Organizer for Google Code-in 2018 & Google Season of Docs 2019, Scholarship Administrator, Code Mentor, Social Media Manager, Copy Editor, Documentation Writer, Code Reviewer
- PostgresOpen Conference Organizer [Jan 2016 Jan 2020] Website Manager, Social Media Manager, Presenter, Developer Advocate, Copy Editor, Marketing & Outreach
  - Created Websites: PostgresOpen 2016, PostgresOpen 2017, PostgresOpen 2018, PostgresOpen 2019
  - $\circ$  **Presented:** Securing Your Database in Amazon RDS - <u>Video</u> - <u>Slides</u>
  - Presented: The Three Musketeers Authentication, Authorization, and Accounting - <u>Video</u> - <u>Slides</u>

Availability: 24 hours a day, 7

days a week **Location:** Remote

Time Zone: Pacific Time Zone

Email:

sarah.beth.conway@gmail.com

#### Website:

https://sarahinsandiego.github.i
o/portfolio/

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Git/GitHub, HTML, CSS, SCSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, React JS, Alpine JS, Slides JS, Bootstrap, Reactstrap, Tailwind, ES6, APIs, TypeScript, Python, Go, Bash, Shell, JSON, Linux, Unix, Windows, HubSpot, Hugo, Express, Heroku, Apache, Django, NodeJS, Vagrant, Virtualization, Yarn, Jest, Cypress, PostgreSQL, Kubernetes, OpenShift, Docker, Katacoda, Google Cloud Platform, AWS, Patternfly, ChartJS, OpenLayers, Google Charts, ESLint, Prettier, LaTeX, Pandoc, ASCII, Markdown, Wiki, G Suite, Microsoft Suite, SEO, Google Ad Words, Google Tag Manager, Google Analytics, OSTicket, High Availability, Scalability, Accessibility, Performance, User Experience (UX) and Design, User Interfaces (UI), Responsiveness, Single Page Applications (SPAs)

#### RELATIONAL SKILLS

Digital Marketing, Social
Media Management, Customer
Service, Project Owner,
Program Management, Teacher,
Content Editing, Content
Writing, Code Mentorship,
Code Review, Webinars,
Presentations, Information
Architecture, Documentation,
Developer Evangelism, Agile,
Scrum, Linear, Slack

## **EDUCATION**

```
Western Governors University, Remote - Bachelor's Degree -
Information Technology / Cyber & Computer Forensics and
Counterterrorism

JULY 2017 - DECEMBER 2019

Cuyamaca College, San Diego, CA - Associate's Degree - Network
Administration

JULY 2011 - JUNE 2015

Cuyamaca College, San Diego, CA - Associate's Degree -
Telecommunications

JULY 2011 - JUNE 2015
```

## **CERTIFICATES**

Professional Certificates & Licenses:

- EC-Council Certified Encryption Specialist
- CIWcertified Web Security Associate
- ISC2 Systems Security Certified Practitioner
- Cuyamaca College Computer Support Technician
- Cuyamaca College Telecommunications Networking Technician
- Cuyamaca College Computer Network Administration
- CompTIA Project+ (Expired Jul 2021)
- CompTIA Network+ (Expired Nov 2020)
- CompTIA Security+ (Expired Oct 2020)
- CompTIA A+ (Expired Aug 2020)

## **PORTFOLIO**

Additional screenshots and a list of websites I've contributed to or fully developed can be found on my  $\underline{\text{LinkedIn}}$ ; those found here are isolated examples of my most recent work. All screenshots are partial images of longer webpages and applications.

Crunchy Data

https://imgur.com/a/2ykPUEU

Postgres Open

https://imgur.com/a/ejgiExY

United States PostgreSQL Association (PgUS)

https://imgur.com/a/diIZTQC